[{"answer": "How's that", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You'll leave ", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Arright, let lim go. Cite him for rolling the stop ... And cite old that place for driving to endanger ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Just like that. Quit your bellyaching, my friend ... And let's wrap this up ..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What kind of job... ", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "A boost? What's my friend doing on a boost", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "How'd you get here? Your Moms give you ride ", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You boosted a 'Vette? Then where is it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " So you want to run that part by me again about things being", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh. You maybe have more than one enemy who owns a ca", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So what are you gonna do", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "\"About what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He's gonna kill you", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You can handle it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can handle i", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I can handle i", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You can handle it", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You can handle it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I can handle i", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I can handle i", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You have a Hollandaise sauce ", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Speak for yourself, boss I don't have a Hollandaise sauc", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hello, Otto ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Of course. Hi, my frien", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You spread it out ... you move around... So's they can't touch you... so's they don't know... Shadow games and shit ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Shadow games ..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " my friend", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No. You were replaced by my friend was replaced by my friend. Who was replaced by my friend. Who was replaced by my friend..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " You should leav", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "On account of me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, take it bac", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Take it back, Fre", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Okay, then. I'll catch you later, my friend ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Right ..", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " What do you got there", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What time of year", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Who's that ", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "The Sphinx", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Okay. We're all here. Today's Wednesday. ", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "We're going shopping", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Very good. But what was the significance of", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "His first name was my friend. my friend Magnum..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I go with yo", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "That's what I want ..", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Cos there were those dark days, when I figured", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "No ... ", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "No way ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "No ..", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "The family that steals together, deals together..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Maybe not. But Dad was from another era..", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Dad'd be prou", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What era was that ", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "You're going hig", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "\"Unlock my butto", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "They're factory alarms ... Easy to get around... For a man with... Skills..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Cut 'em..", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Hear you roar ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Let me worry about The Club ..", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " 200 K. Just like we said ..", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "But I had to. It was the only way to get to yo", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Do you believe this", "docId": "gone_in_60_seconds.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "We gotta do what we gotta d", "qsentId": 64}]